creditinfocenter.com 2019-10-30

# Privacy and Acceptable Use Policy For Credit Info Center

###### Written by: Kristy Welsh

## Credit Info, LLC Takes Your Privacy Seriously

### What This Policy Covers

The creditinfocenter.com website is owned by Credit Info, LLC. This privacy policy covers Credit Info, LLC's treatment of personally identifiable information that Credit Info Center collects when you are on our site and when you use Credit Info Center's services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Credit Info, LLC does not own or control, or to people that Credit Info, LLC does not employ or manage.

### Information Collection and Use

Credit Info Center collects personally identifiable information when you use our discussion boards, purchase products, or send us email. Information collected will include, but not be limited to: your name, e-mail address, the website which referred you to us, and the internet service provider you use, IP address, mailing address and phone numbers. At no time will we sell this information to any third party.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

Credit Info Center does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user accesses or visits, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. Cookies are small text files and we may use both Session Cookies (that track how you use our website) and Persistent Cookies that stay after you close your browser and may be used when you come back to visit.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Credit Info, LLC will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone unless:

  * We have your consent to share the information.
  * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process.
  * We find that your actions on our websites violate the Credit Info, LLC terms of service, or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

Google and the [DoubleClick DART cookie](https://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx):

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

### Our Advertising Partners

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies on our site. Our advertising partners include, but are not limited to: Lexington Law, Google, BankRate. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on our site and send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see. We have no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

Credit Info, LLC may edit this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.

  * #### Categories

  * #### Connect with us.

Copyright © 2018 Credit InfoCenter [About Us](https://www.creditinfocenter.com/about/) | [Contact Us](https://www.creditinfocenter.com/about/contact-us.php) | [Privacy](https://www.creditinfocenter.com/privacy.shtml) | [Press Releases](https://www.creditinfocenter.com/pressreleases/) | [Site Map](https://www.creditinfocenter.com/sitemap.shtml)

Disclaimer: Credit Info, LLC may be compensated in exchange for featured placement of certain sponsored ads and services, or your clicking on certain links posted on this website.

® Credit Info, LLC. All Rights Reserved.
